Owolabi Toba Samuel

Fullstack Developer

Lagos, Nigeria +2348162977243,+2347061409595 owolabitoba31@gmail.com github.com/Thobatech31 linkedin.com/in/toba-owolabi-466316205

Summary

FullStack Developer offering 3+ years of experience providing technical support to startups building digital solutions. Proficient in translating designs and wireframes into higher quality code and writing application interface code via Javascript, ReactJs workflows and also employed a variety of languages such as NodeJs, Javascript, PHP (FatFree), Html, Css and Bootstrap to write and create user-friendly web applications. Excels working in a team environment and ability to learn rapidly.

Experience

FullStack Developer November 2019 - PRESENT

Elta-Solutions. Lagos State Nigeria.

Focusing on building web apps using reactJs and PHP (Fatfree).

- Developing the latest user-interface features using ReactJs and built reusable components for use.
- Optimizing components for maximum performance across a vast of web capable devices and browsers.
- ❖ Involved in architecting solutions along with other team members.

Intern Web Developer July 2016 - January 2017 Coven Works Ltd.

Intern Web Developer Coven Works Limited.

❖ Assisted in providing support and offering advice for all technical issues raised. Assisted in the creation of lander pages for adverts Rendered support for all computer based activities.

Education

Federal University of Technology Akure, Nigeria. 2013 - 2018 Bachelor of Technology, Computer science.

Second Class (Upper Division).

Carried a thesis on Platform As a Service (Paas) and Saas Architecture.

Academic Qualifications

National Youth Service Corps. (N.Y.S.C) Discharge Certificate 2019 - 2020

Projects

<u>Expensa</u>

Link: https://develop.d3v4luort70rus.amplifyapp.com

Description: A financial Management Application.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

<u>Gamepride</u>

Link: https://gamepride.co

Admin Link: https://admin.gamepride.co/

Description: An online game platform to play against anyone, earn money and

earn respect.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

<u>Artsave</u>

Link: https://artsave.elta.solutions/

Admin Link: https://artsave-admin.elta.solutions/

Description: An online game platform to play against anyone, earn money and

earn respect.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

<u>Agbedowo</u>

Link: http://dev.agbedowo.com/about-us

Description: An online agricultural fair-trader platform, connecting farmers to

3

industries all around the world.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

Recallomobile

Link: https://recallomobile.elta.solutions

Description: A Call Management Application that was built to route inbound and

outbound calls intelligently for users.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

CAC Checker App

Link: https://company-checker.netlify.app

Description: An online App for verifying businesses using their CAC serial No.

Technology: ReactJs.

Ecommerce Shopping Api's

Link: https://documenter.getpostman.com/view/10804592/UVeAw9Bs#1925fa6

8-9afe-46ed-9514-bc6eef8250c1

Description: An online based ecommerce shopping platform to buy products

and make a payment using Stripe payment gateway.

Technology: NodeJs.

ChurchSpace Api's

Link:https://documenter.getpostman.com/view/10804592/UVkgwIjI

Description: An Online web based platform where churches can manage

their daily, weekly and monthly activities etc. and make use of Paystack and Dojah payment system

Technology: NodeJs.

<u>Ropay</u>

Link: https://ropay.ng/

Description: An Online web based platform to compute advance payroll, statutory compliance, automate salaries, pay employees, remit pension and disburse airtime for employees.

Technology: PHP (FatFree) / Javascript.

Rohealth

Link: https://rohealth.ng/

Description: An Online web based platform to **Give your employees greater** decision-making control over their health insurance, while at the same time saving your business 20–30% in costs.

Technology: PHP (FatFree) / Javascript.

Evermissed

Link: http://server.elta.com.ng/evermissed

Description: An Online web based platform for honouring and celebrating memorable lives.

Technology: PHP (FatFree).

<u>Kedesa Whogohost</u>

Link: http://server.elta.com.ng/kedesa_whogohost

Description: An Online web based platform to send Bulk SMS (messages),

Airtime etc.

Technology: PHP (FatFree).

Church Management App

Link: http://server.elta.com.ng/churchmanagementapp

Description: An Online web based platform where churches can manage their

daily, weekly and monthly activities etc.

Technology: PHP (FatFree).

Core Competencies

JavaScript,ReactJs,NodeJs,Mongoose, PHP, FatFree, Html, Git, CSS, Bootstrap.

4